{"data":{"site":{"pathPrefix":"/restaurant-inspections"},"postgres":{"establishment":[{"establishmentid":"949","name":"Detroit International Academy/ Northern","address":"9026 Woodward Ave","zipcode":"48202","owner":"Board of education","licenseNumber":"064102","licenseType":"Fixed Establishment","establishmentType":"Public School","establishmentStatus":"Open","riskCategory":null,"reviewFrequencyDays":"210.0","coords":"-83.07980,42.38264","geojson":{"id":"949","type":"Feature","geometry":{"type":"Point","coordinates":[-83.079795896,42.3826362470001]},"properties":{"name":"Detroit International Academy/ Northern","owner":"Board of education","address":"9026 Woodward Ave","zipcode":"48202","license_type":"Fixed Establishment","risk_category":null,"license_number":"064102","establishmentid":"949","establishment_type":"Public School","establishment_status":"Open","review_frequency_days":"210.0","most_recent_license_date":"5/15/2017"}},"nearbyList":[{"establishmentid":"4881","name":"Cleary University","address":"8904 Woodward Ave","zipcode":"48202"},{"establishmentid":"2006","name":"Subway","address":"9320 Woodward Ave","zipcode":"48202"},{"establishmentid":"5267","name":"Ocean Splash Fish & Chicken","address":"8528 Woodward Ave","zipcode":"48202"},{"establishmentid":"4015","name":"Greater New Mount Moriah","address":"586 Owens St","zipcode":"48202"},{"establishmentid":"1717","name":"The Turkey Grill","address":"8290 Woodward Ave","zipcode":"48202"},{"establishmentid":"51622495","name":"The Turkey Grill Food Truck","address":"8290 Woodward Ave","zipcode":"48202"},{"establishmentid":"753","name":"Burger King ","address":"8201 Woodward Ave","zipcode":"48202"},{"establishmentid":"4376","name":"Mount Zion New Covenant Baptist Church","address":"8231 Second Ave","zipcode":"48202"},{"establishmentid":"5204","name":"Miss Virginia's Ice Cream Parlor","address":"8801 Oakland Ave","zipcode":"48211"},{"establishmentid":"3892","name":"Evans Solutions","address":"8045 Second","zipcode":"48202"}],"inspectionsByEstablishmentidList":[{"inspectionid":"43926","inspectionDate":"2018-10-10T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"6-501.12","violationDescription":"(A) PHYSICAL FACILITIES shall be cleaned as often as necessary to keep them clean.\r\n(B) Except spill cleanup, cleaning shall be done during periods when the least amount of FOOD is exposed such as after closing. ","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Physical facilities/structures","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Soiled","subProblem":"","location":"FACILITY","subLocation":"","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Clean."},{"violationCode":"6-501.112","violationDescription":"Dead or trapped birds, insects, rodents, and other pests shall be removed from control devices and the PREMISES at a frequency that prevents their accumulation,  decomposition, or the attraction of pests.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Dead/trapped pest(s)","subItem":"rodents mice","problemDescription":"Not removed from facility","subProblem":"","location":"STORAGE ROOM","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":"2018-10-10T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Remove from facility/premises."},{"violationCode":"4-501.11","violationDescription":"EQUIPMENT shall be maintained in a state of repair and condition that meets the requirements of the code.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Equipment","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Broken","subProblem":"","location":"WALK-IN COOLER","subLocation":"","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Repair/replace."}]},{"inspectionid":"41931","inspectionDate":"2018-03-20T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"No","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"5-103.11","violationDescription":"(A) The water source and system shall be of sufficient capacity to meet the peak water demands of the FOOD ESTABLISHMENT. (Pf)\r\n(B) Hot water generation and distribution systems shall be sufficient to meet the peak hot water demands throughout the FOOD ESTABLISHMENT. (Pf)\r\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Hot water supply","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Insufficient to meet demands","subProblem":"","location":"SINKS","subLocation":"Throughout","corrected":"No","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Provide sufficient supply if hot water such as a larger or additional hot water heater."},{"violationCode":"6-501.111","violationDescription":"The presence of insects, rodents, and other pests shall be controlled to minimize their presence on the PREMISES.  by:\r\n(A) Routinely inspecting incoming shipments of FOOD and supplies; \r\n(B) Routinely inspecting the PREMISES for evidence of pests;\r\n(C) Using methods, if pests are found, such as trapping devices or other means of pest control as specified.(Pf) \r\n(D) Eliminating harborage conditions. \r\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Pest(s)","subItem":"rodents rats","problemDescription":null,"subProblem":"","location":"OUTSIDE PREMISES","subLocation":"","corrected":"No","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Remove pests from facility."}]},{"inspectionid":"40167","inspectionDate":"2017-09-26T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"3-501.16","violationDescription":"Except during preparation, cooking, or cooling, or when time is used as the public health control POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD) shall be maintained:\r\n(A)  135ºF or above, except that roasts properly cooked and cooled may be held              at a temperature of 130ºF; or (P)\r\n(B)   At 41ºF or less (P)\r\n","violationType":"Priority","itemDescription":"Cold food item(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Stored above 41 degrees F","subProblem":"","location":"WALK-IN COOLER","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2017-09-26T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Discard"},{"violationCode":"4-501.11","violationDescription":"EQUIPMENT shall be maintained in a state of repair and condition that meets the requirements of the code.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Equipment","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Broken","subProblem":"","location":"WALK-IN COOLER","subLocation":"","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Repair/replace."},{"violationCode":"4-204.112","violationDescription":"(A)  In a mechanically refrigerated or hot FOOD storage unit, the sensor of a TEMPERATURE MEASURING DEVICE shall be located to measure the air temperature in the warmest part of a mechanically refrigerated unit and in the coolest part of a hot FOOD storage unit.\r\n(B)  Cold or hot holding EQUIPMENT used for POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD shall be designed to include and shall be equipped with at least one integral or permanently affixed TEMPERATURE MEASURING DEVICE that is located to allow easy viewing of the device's temperature display (EXCEPT, heat lamps, cold plates, steam tables, or other equipment where it is not practical).\r\n(C)  TEMPERATURE MEASURING DEVICES shall be designed to be easily readable.\r\n(D)  FOOD TEMPERATURE MEASURING DEVICES and water TEMPERATURE MEASURING DEVICES on WAREWASHING machines shall have a numerical scale, printed record, or digital readout in increments no greater than 1C or 2F in the intended range of use. (Pf)\r\n\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Thermometer(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"","location":"COOLERS THROUGHOUT","subLocation":"","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Provide as required"}]},{"inspectionid":"38886","inspectionDate":"2017-04-26T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"3-307.11","violationDescription":"FOOD shall be protected from contamination that may result from a factor or source not specified under Subparts 3-301 - 3-306.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Food","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not protected","subProblem":"From contamination","location":"SERVICE AREA-SECONDARY","subLocation":"","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Protect against contamination"},{"violationCode":"6-501.12","violationDescription":"(A) PHYSICAL FACILITIES shall be cleaned as often as necessary to keep them clean.\r\n(B) Except spill cleanup, cleaning shall be done during periods when the least amount of FOOD is exposed such as after closing. ","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Physical facilities/structures","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Soiled","subProblem":"","location":"FACILITY","subLocation":"","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Clean."}]},{"inspectionid":"37168","inspectionDate":"2016-11-15T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[]}]}]}},"pageContext":{"eid":"949"}}